Nicki Padar
Visual and Product Designer

nickipadar.com
nickipadar@gmail.com
(510) 304-5890
linkedin.com/in/nicki-padar

EDUCATION
University of California, Davis
Design B.A.
Cognitive Science B.S.

March 2018 - Cum Laude

EXPERIENCE
Udacity
Visual Designer
September 2018 - Present
Design and ship web/mobile features to improve usability and increase purchase rates. Develop user flows, wireframes, and prototypes for growth marketing pages. Develop hypothesis for lead generation A/B testing.
Visual Design Intern
May 2018 - August 2018
Designed and prototyped assets for social media, ads, email marketing, and website. Conceptualized and managed the redesign of the student success landing page to create optimal visual and user experience.

Seagate Technology
Graphic Design Intern 
June 2017 - March 2018
Designed deliverables such as flyers, timelines, pamphlets, etc. for employees and managers to use. Managed the redesign of the human resources website. Improved the user experience of the website by creating a cleaner interface.

The California Aggie
Layout Artist
September 2017 - March 2018
Designed deliverables such as flyers, timelines, pamphlets, etc. for employees and managers to use. Managed the redesign of the human resources website. Improved the user experience of the website by creating a cleaner interface.
Graphic Designer
November 2016 - August 2017
Designed graphics/infographics for weekly news stories to be shown in print and on the website.

SKILLS
Design 
Branding
Typography
Prototyping
User Experience
User Interaction
Product Design
Visual Design
Motion Design

Tools
Sketch
InVision
Photoshop
Illustrator
InDesign
After Effects
HTML/CSS
Bootstrap
Social Media

